Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪The moon rests on the treetops, listening to the evening breeze♪
♪يستقر القمر على قمم الأشجار، ويستمع إلى نسيم المساء♪
♪Wine in hand, I sing as stars shine in disarray♪
♪ النبيذ في يدي، أغني بينما تتألق النجوم في حالة من الفوضى ♪
♪The endless night keeps but one lonely lamp♪
♪الليل الذي لا ينتهي لا يحتفظ إلا بمصباح وحيد♪
♪Who knows if I'm warm or cold♪
♪من يدري إن كنت دافئًا أم باردًا♪
♪Years of companionship vanish like mist♪
♪سنوات من الرفقة تتلاشى مثل الضباب♪
♪How many roads must a deep love travel♪
♪كم عدد الطرق التي يجب أن يسلكها الحب العميق؟♪
♪The returned soul wears robes of regret♪
♪الروح العائدة ترتدي رداء الندم♪
♪Brushing off dust with a wave♪
♪إزالة الغبار بموجة♪
♪Wind or no wind, I think of you♪
♪ ريح أو لا ريح، أفكر فيك♪
♪Beyond words♪
♪ما وراء الكلمات♪
♪A vow is cherished all the time♪
♪إن العهد يُعتز به في كل الأوقات♪
♪Some souls yearn to ferment time♪
♪بعض النفوس تتوق إلى تخمير الوقت♪
♪Into a story♪
♪في قصة♪
♪Crushing the past, I let old memories fade♪
♪سحق الماضي، أترك الذكريات القديمة تتلاشى♪
♪Don't let this story end♪
♪لا تدع هذه القصة تنتهي♪
=Beyond The Loop=
=خارج الحلقة=
=Episode 17=
=الحلقة 17=
Wan is your biological daughter.
وان هي ابنتك البيولوجية.
It's really Wan!
إنه وان حقا!
Wonderful!
رائع!
It's Wan!
إنه وان!
But I haven't told her yet.
ولكنني لم أخبرها بعد.
Don't. At least not now.
لا تفعل ذلك. على الأقل ليس الآن.
Mother.
الأم.
How is Miss Yu?
كيف حال السيدة يو؟
She's much better.
إنها أفضل بكثير.
Would you like to see her?
هل ترغب برؤيتها؟
Yes, I'll check on her.
نعم، سأتحقق منها.
Qiming, it's late now.
تشيمينغ، لقد أصبح الوقت متأخرًا الآن.
Let Miss Yu rest early.
دع الآنسة يو ترتاح مبكرًا.
I'll just check on her and leave soon.
سأتحقق منها ثم أغادر قريبًا.
Qiming, don't forget
تشيمينغ، لا تنسى
she's now the City Lord's wife.
وهي الآن زوجة سيد المدينة.
Mother, I know.
أمي، أنا أعلم.
I'm just bringing her some food.
أنا فقط أحضر لها بعض الطعام.
Don't think
لا افكر
I don't know what you're thinking about.
لا أعلم ماذا تفكر فيه.
Stop embarrassing me!
توقف عن إحراجي!
Mother, why do you say that?
أمي لماذا تقولين ذلك؟
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدا،
stop pursuing Miss Yu.
توقف عن ملاحقة الآنسة يو.
Just give up on her!
فقط استسلم لها!
Mother.
الأم.
You approved of her
لقد وافقت عليها
and encouraged me to pursue her before.
وشجعتني على متابعتها من قبل.
You wanted me to pursue her,
لقد أردتني أن أتابعها،
then I had to.
ثم كان علي أن أفعل ذلك.
Now you ask me
الآن تسألني
to give up on her?
للتخلي عنها؟
Why?
لماذا؟
Miss Yu is your elder sister.
السيدة يو هي أختك الكبرى.
Mother.
الأم.
What did you say?
ماذا قلت؟
Miss Yu is my Baozhu,
الآنسة يو هي باوزهو الخاصة بي،
my daughter,
ابنتي
your biological sister.
أختك البيولوجية.
Mother.
الأم.
You're lying, right?
أنت تكذب، أليس كذلك؟
Tell me you're lying.
أخبرني أنك تكذب.
Mother, tell me you're lying.
أمي، أخبريني أنك تكذبين.
Qiming! Qiming!
تشيمينغ! تشيمينغ!
Liar!
كذاب!
Qiming!
تشيمينغ!
Liar! You are all liars!
كاذبون! أنتم جميعًا كاذبون!
- Qiming. - City Lord!
- تشيمينغ. - سيد المدينة!
Let him go.
دعوه يذهب.
Your time has come!
لقد حان وقتك!
Lady! Lady!
سيدتي! سيدتي!
Yunqing.
يونتشينغ.
Why are you here?
لماذا انت هنا؟
Yuanbao said you were practicing here,
قال يوانباو أنك كنت تتدرب هنا،
and I brought you an outer robe.
وأحضرت لك رداءً خارجيًا.
I've made soup.
لقد صنعت حساءً.
Come home for some.
تعال إلى المنزل لبعض الوقت.
Alright, as you wish.
حسنًا، كما تريد.
(Shili Pavilion)
(جناح شيلي)
Mr. Song.
السيد سونغ.
Let me toast you.
دعني أشرب نخبًا لك.
Here!
هنا!
- A toast to you, Mr. Song! - Tonight, we drink until...
- نخب لك، سيد سونغ! - الليلة، نشرب حتى...
- Okay.
- حسنًا.
we drop!
نحن نسقط!
Mr. Song.
السيد سونغ.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Mr. Song, are you okay?
السيد سونغ هل أنت بخير؟
Two more cups?
كوبين اضافيين؟
You're so beautiful,
ًأنت جميلة جدا،
just like her.
مثلها تماما.
Mr. Song, who is she?
السيد سونغ، من هي؟
It's... She...
إنها...هي...
Everyone out!
الجميع خارجا!
Yes.
نعم.
Why are you leaving?
لماذا تغادر؟
Qiming! Stop running wild.
تشيمينغ! توقف عن الجري الجامح.
I'm not.
انا لست كذلك.
I just
انا فقط
feel upset.
أشعر بالانزعاج.
She's your sister.
إنها أختك.
That's a solid fact.
هذه حقيقة ثابتة.
You shouldn't have given birth to me,
لا كان ينبغي عليك أن تلدني،
then I wouldn't be suffering like this!
حينها لن أعاني هكذا!
You...
أنت...
Qiming! Qiming!
تشيمينغ! تشيمينغ!
I'm tired.
أنا متعب.
Please go back.
من فضلك عد إلى الوراء.
Qiming, do you resent me?
تشيمينغ، هل أنت مستاء مني؟
I can't tell
لا أستطيع أن أقول
whether I resent you,
سواء كنت مستاء منك،
or I resent myself.
أو أنا أستاء من نفسي.
Wan, you must be exhausted.
وان، لا بد أنك مرهق.
Have an orange.
خذ برتقالة.
No.
لا.
Then you must want grapes!
إذن أنت بالتأكيد تريد العنب!
No, you eat them.
لا، أنت تأكلهم.
How about some tea?
ماذا عن بعض الشاي؟
No.
لا.
I know you're worried about my health.
أعلم أنك قلق بشأن صحتي.
Look, I'm perfectly fine.
انظر، أنا بخير تماما.
I feel happy in making money.
أشعر بالسعادة في كسب المال.
Let me calculate
دعني احسب
how much I earned yesterday.
كم كسبت بالأمس؟
You're so busy.
أنت مشغول جداً.
I feel terrible.
أنا أشعر بالرعب.
I'll give you anything.
سأعطيك أي شيء.
Just talk to me.
فقط تحدث معي.
Be good. I'll talk to you tonight.
كن بخير، سأتحدث معك الليلة.
But I can't wait until night.
ولكنني لا أستطيع الانتظار حتى الليل.
Mr. Song, what brings you here?
السيد سونغ، ما الذي أتى بك إلى هنا؟
Mr. Song. Long time no see.
السيد سونغ، لم نلتقي منذ زمن.
Long time no see.
وقت طويل لا رؤية.
I'll go buy
سأذهب للشراء
some apricots.
بعض المشمش.
We have plenty of fruit.
لدينا الكثير من الفاكهة.
Mu Yunqing has been acting so strangely.
لقد كان مو يونتشينغ يتصرف بغرابة شديدة.
Mr. Song, please sit.
السيد سونغ، من فضلك اجلس.
Miss Yu, are you feeling better?
آنسة يو، هل تشعرين بتحسن؟
Much better.
أفضل بكثير.
Full of energy now.
مليئة بالطاقة الآن.
Does he treat you well?
هل يعاملك جيدا؟
He treats me great.
يعاملني بشكل رائع.
Just needs some adaptation.
يحتاج فقط إلى بعض التكيف.
Good.
جيد.
I'm glad to hear that.
يسعدني سماع ذلك.
How have you been lately, Mr. Song?
كيف حالك في الآونة الأخيرة، سيد سونغ؟
Very well.
جيد جدا.
What brings you here today?
ما الذي أتى بك إلى هنا اليوم؟
Just to check on you.
فقط للاطمئنان عليك.
If City Lord ever mistreats you,
إذا أساء سيد المدينة معاملتك يومًا ما،
tell me and I'll deal with him.
أخبرني وسوف أتعامل معه.
No need. I can deal with him myself.
لا داعي لذلك، أستطيع التعامل معه بنفسي.
Thank you, Mr. Song.
شكرا لك سيد سونغ.
I'll take my leave now.
سوف آخذ إجازتي الآن.
Mr. Song.
السيد سونغ.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
(I hope you can always)
(أتمنى أن تتمكن من ذلك دائمًا)
(be happy.)
(كن سعيدا.)
(My sister.)
(أختي.)
Husband.
زوج.
Is this too cruel for Qiming?
هل هذا قاسي جدًا بالنسبة لـ تشيمينغ؟
I also feel pitiful for Qiming.
أنا أيضا أشعر بالشفقة على تشيمينغ.
But only he can
ولكن هو فقط من يستطيع
overcome this obstacle himself.
التغلب على هذه العقبة بنفسه.
Fate plays cruel tricks.
القدر يلعب خدعة قاسية.
If he truly understands,
إذا كان يفهم حقا،
I'll never force him
لن أجبره أبدًا
to help me avenge you.
لمساعدتي على الانتقام لك.
I'll let him live as he desires.
سأتركه يعيش كما يريد.
Mother.
الأم.
Rest assured.
اطمئن، لا تشغل بالك.
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدا،
I can only be Yu Yingwan's brother.
لا يمكنني أن أكون سوى شقيق يو ينغوان.
And I'll never forget avenging Father.
ولن أنسى أبدًا انتقام أبي.
Mobei will pay for what they did.
سوف تدفع موباي ثمن ما فعلته.
Qiming, I've wronged you.
تشيمينغ، لقد ظلمتك.
Though we've found your sister,
على الرغم من أننا وجدنا أختك،
I feel I've failed you.
أشعر أنني خذلتك.
You shouldn't bear such cruel reality.
لا يجب عليك أن تتحمل مثل هذا الواقع القاسي.
Mother, actually,
الأم، في الواقع،
I've always wanted to meet my sister.
لقد أردت دائمًا مقابلة أختي.
Today my wish came true.
اليوم تحققت أمنيتي.
I'm happy
انا سعيد
we found her at last.
لقد وجدناها أخيرا.
She must be happy too.
لابد وأن تكون سعيدة أيضاً.
The City Lord's Mansion just sent word,
لقد أرسل قصر سيد المدينة للتو كلمة،
saying your sister is pregnant.
قول أن أختك حامل.
From now on, we must
من الآن فصاعدا، يجب علينا
care for your sister,
اعتني بأختك
and the child she carries.
والطفل الذي تحمله.
I know what to do.
انا اعرف ماذا افعل.
Qiming, I know you feel upset.
تشيمينغ، أعلم أنك تشعر بالانزعاج.
But this is what life is.
ولكن هذه هي الحياة.
Qiming, you have a long road ahead.
تشيمينغ، لديك طريق طويل أمامك.
I believe you'll finally clarify this
أعتقد أنك ستوضح هذا الأمر أخيرًا
and find your own happiness.
وإيجاد سعادتك الخاصة.
Mother, I understand.
أمي، أنا أفهم.
Rest assured.
اطمئن، لا تشغل بالك.
I'll treat my sister well.
سأعامل أختي جيدًا.
Trust me.
ثق بي.
♪Winter snow waltzes before the courtyard♪
♪رقصة ثلوج الشتاء أمام الفناء♪
♪Palaces show no mercy♪
♪القصور لا ترحم♪
♪So much courage it takes♪
♪يتطلب الأمر الكثير من الشجاعة♪
♪To retrace each step♪
♪لإعادة تتبع كل خطوة♪
♪Memory's whispers, dreams or illusion♪
♪همسات الذاكرة، أحلام أو وهم♪
♪Butterflies climb mountains for love♪
♪الفراشات تتسلق الجبال من أجل الحب♪
♪Perish before the flowers♪
♪يموت قبل الزهور♪
♪You seem so distant, yet right before my eyes♪
♪تبدو بعيدًا جدًا، ومع ذلك، أمام عيني مباشرة♪
♪A game of chess, a fate of strife♪
♪لعبة شطرنج، مصير الصراع♪
♪I dream of standing with you, side by side♪
♪أحلم بالوقوف معك جنبًا إلى جنب♪
♪If you would meet me face to face♪
♪إذا قابلتني وجها لوجه♪
♪I'd die without a single regret♪
♪سأموت دون ندم واحد♪
♪You're the untouchable star♪
♪أنت النجم الذي لا يمكن المساس به♪
♪I'm the tiniest speck♪
♪أنا أصغر بقعة♪
♪Through all the tides of love and hate♪
♪من خلال كل موجات الحب والكراهية♪
♪Our eyes met across the mortal world♪
♪التقت أعيننا عبر العالم البشري♪
♪When breezes stirred by my window♪
♪عندما تحركت النسمات بجانب نافذتي♪
♪Cherry blossoms rained in the sky♪
♪أزهار الكرز أمطرت السماء♪
♪You're the distant star♪
♪أنت النجم البعيد♪
♪I'm the tiniest speck♪
♪أنا أصغر بقعة♪
♪Spend all my devotion♪
♪أقضي كل إخلاصي♪
♪For your tears and embrace♪
♪لدموعك وعناقك♪
♪I'll brave all the blizzards♪
♪سأتحدى كل العواصف الثلجية♪
♪To walk with you♪
♪للمشي معك♪